# Ha Son Nguyen, Web Developer

SOCIAL LINKS	<u>LinkedIn</u> , <u>Github</u>	
PROFILE	Recent graduate with nearly 2 years of experience in web development. Highly adaptable, have contributed projects spanning diverse domains and various technology stacks, from modern frameworks (React.js & Laravel) to legacy code base (Java Servlets). Skilled in both English and Japanese, enabling efforts communication and collaboration in diverse professional environments.	Vue.js,
	Contact	
	<ul> <li>Phone: 0915836470</li> <li>Email: hson181001@gmail.com</li> </ul>	
EDUCATION		
2016 — 2019	HNUE High School For Gifted Student	
	<ul> <li>Chemistry Major</li> <li>Graduated With CPA of 9.1</li> </ul>	
2019 — 2024	Hanoi University of Science and Technology	
	<ul> <li>HESPI K64</li> <li>Software Engineer Major</li> <li>Graduated with CPA of 3.14</li> </ul>	
WORKING EXPERIENCE		
Feb 2024 — Present	Full Stack Web Developer, Digi Dinos	Hanoi
	08/2024 - Present: Developer – Business Trip Planning Project	
	<ul> <li>Contributed to the development of a business trip planning system used by more than 600 com including large Japanese enterprises</li> <li>Collaborated directly with Japanese team members via chat to manage and complete tasks</li> <li>Configured development servers, resolved issues, analyzed shell scripts, and wrote technical documentation</li> <li>Technologies: Java, Oracle, Linux, Shell Script, Git, GitHub Actions, Tomcat</li> </ul>	panies,
	02/2024 - 07/2024: Developer – Medical Equipment Manufacturing Company	
	<ul> <li>Developed new features, fixed bugs for various web applications as a full stack developer</li> <li>Helped create various tools and scripts to automate business processes</li> <li>Developed a sending emails website from scratch for customer's internal organization</li> <li>Technologies: PHP (Laravel), Javascript (Vue.js 3), MySQL, Git, GitLab, VBA &amp; Google App S</li> </ul>	Script
Sep 2023 — Jan 2024	Full Stack Web Developer Intern, Digi Dinos	Hanoi
	<ul> <li>Acquired expertise in the company's tech stack, including multiple programming languages and frameworks</li> <li>Assisted with small tasks on the company's project management web application</li> <li>Was awarded Intern of the Year</li> </ul>	
Mar 2023 — Jun 2023	Backend Web Developer Intern, Pixta Vietnam	Hanoi
	<ul> <li>Went through Ruby on Rails training program, obtained fundamental coding skills and core web</li> <li>Interacted with a large stock photos web application system, with 1.3 million users worldwide</li> <li>Gained understanding about real-world web application architecture and functionality</li> </ul>	concepts

## General Programming Skill:

- 4 years of general coding experience
- Have solid understanding about data structures and algorithms
- Proficient in C/C++ programming language

#### Others:

- Had experience in image segmentation and implementing deep learning models
- Finished an image segmentation project with a customized Vietnamese drone dataset as graduation thesis

#### LANGUAGES

## English - Fluent

Strong written and verbal communication skills, could enable effective collaboration and clear documentation.

## Japanese - Intermediate

Could read and understand documentation, and form basic conversation. Willing to become proficient in Japanese to better serve work purposes.

### CERTIFICATION

## IELTS 8.0

Issued May 2023

JLPT N3

Issued Dec 2022